icovia.com 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy

2020 is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Indeed, protection of your data is one of the key success criteria by which we measure our performance. And we believe that these policies should be fully disclosed to the public. This privacy policy is based on our belief that customer information should be handled with the utmost respect and should only be shared with other organizations only with the express authorization of our customers. Simply put, we do not sell customer lists or related customer information to other companies. 

In as far as this represents best practice on the web, 2020 is committed to complying with these standards so that members can feel secure in the knowledge that their personal data is properly managed. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact 2020 Icovia Customer Support via the contact form at http://www.icovia.com/contact.aspx. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, please contact our Customer Advocate at (+1) 866-698-2020. 

This document discloses the privacy practices for the 2020 Icovia Space Planner and icovia.com including: - What personally identifiable information of yours is collected - What organization is collecting the information - How the information is used - With whom the information may be shared - What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information - What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Icovia's control - How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

Questions regarding this privacy policy should be directed to 2020 via our contact form at http://www.icovia.com/contact.aspx. 

Table of Contents

1\. Information We Collect   
2\. Our Use of Your Information   
3\. Opt-Out of Email Communications   
4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information   
5\. "Email a Plan" Feature   
6\. Control of Your Password   
7\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information   
8\. Other Information Collectors   
9\. Security   
10\. Changes to Privacy Policy   
11\. Contact Information 

**1\. Information We Collect**

Our primary goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and personalized experience while using our services. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience easier and quicker. 

To fully use our services, you will need to register using our online registration form, where you will be required to provide us with your contact information (e.g. e-mail address) and some other information relating to your professional employment (e.g. name of the company you work for, your position there). We automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our site. We use this information to do internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand and serve our users. This information is compiled and analysed on an aggregated basis. 

Using the Site's web server log files, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, track users' movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our site or not), what browser and operating system you are using, your IP address etc. 

In addition, we use cookies on certain pages of our site. We may also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a cookie. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. The other type of cookie we use is a 'persistent' cookie. This stays on your hard drive and we use this to automatically identify who you are. We use this cookie so that you do not need to log in manually every time you visit the site if you are a registered user. The cookie itself contains no personally identifiable information but it does pass an ID to our server which allows us to tie the cookie to your personal information. We do this to allow us to let you know on the homepage what has changed on the site since your last visit. We also use the cookie to track how often you visit the site so we know who our most loyal users are. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you will not be able to use certain features on our site. For example, if you disable cookies, you will need to log in manually each time you visit the site as we cannot use a cookie to remember who you are. Some of our business partners (e.g. net-filter.com; hitbox.com) use cookies on our site. These are used to monitor site performance and to measure site traffic and usage. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Surveys & Contests. From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys, contests or for a particular service (e.g. newsletter). Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested will include contact information (as supplied to the site during registration) and supplementary information on your professional interests, opinions and preferences (e.g. choice of software, working practices, opinions on industry issues, feedback on 2020 Icovia products and the Icovia web site). We will use the contact information to notify winners. We will not publish winners' details on the site though on request we will provide details of any winners' name and organization. If the survey or contest has a sponsor then we will share information given by entrants with the sponsor. 

Payment Processing. In order to process payments online we require the billing address for the credit card used and our external payment provider, CyberSource, requires your credit card details. For details of how your information is used, please see following section. 

**2\. Our Use of Your Information**

We use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyse site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our site's content, layout, and services. We believe these uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users' needs. 

We use your e-mail address to send you newsletters or other communications that you have requested from the Site. Out of respect for our users we offer an opt-out (see section 3). 

We use information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to resolve any disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. At times, we may look across multiple users to identify problems or resolve disputes. 

Payment Processing. We take online payments for our subscription and membership services. We use CyberSource as our external payment provider. Icovia is also a licensee of GeoTrust, an industry leader providing secure online transactions. In addition to the information outlined above, we require the billing address of the credit card you use so that we can pass this to CyberSource who check the address against the cardholder's details for security purposes. We store these billing details on our servers in case we need to contact you in the future regarding payments. CyberSource requires that you provide your credit card details to process the transaction. This is done on a secure CyberSource server using SSL (secure sockets layer) provided by GeoTrust. In the case of a suspected fraudulent transaction, card details may be accessed by Icovia for the sole purpose of performing further checks. Icovia does not retain these details. These details are stored securely by CyberSource in order to process future payments you may make, but CyberSource does not use your information for any other purpose. 

Your Personal Information is stored in our databases, which are located in the United States. Please note that the information you enter may at some time be transferred outside the United States for the purposes of processing by Icovia or any of its affiliates. By submitting your information, you consent to this transfer. 

**3\. Opt-Out of Email Communications**

If at any stage you wish no longer to receive any e-mails that you receive from the site you can stop them by changing your Icovia account preferences section under "My Account" which can be found by logging in to http://design.icovia.com/login. On this page you can opt out by unchecking the box marked "keep me updated about Icovia product updates and announcements." All product update and announcement emails we send to our customers also include a link to opt out at the bottom of the email. 

**4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**

Unfortunately, due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. 

By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. 

As a general proposition, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party. 

Advertisers. We may aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. 

Legal Requests. 2020 cooperates with law enforcement inquiries and other third parties to enforce laws, intellectual property and other rights. Local, and international law enforcement agents can request and may receive your personally identifiable information. 

Suppliers and Other Service Providers. From time to time we use third party Suppliers and Service Providers to facilitate our services. Where any Service Provider collects information directly from you (such as the situation where we ask a Service Provider to conduct a survey for us) you will be notified of the involvement of the Supplier or Service Provider, and all information disclosures you make will be strictly optional. 

**5\. "Email a Plan" Feature**

2020 Icovia offers a feature whereby you can e-mail a copy of a plan to a friend or colleague. This will involve entering the e-mail address of your friend. We do not use the e-mail addresses you enter for any purpose other than to send your e-mail. We do not store, rent or sell these e-mail addresses. 

**6\. Control of Your Password**

Except as specifically permitted by this section, you may not disclose your 2020 Icovia password to any third parties nor share it with any third parties. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password by visiting the Icovia account preferences section under "My Account" which can be found at http://www.icovia.com/manageaccount.aspx?. If you wish to change your password for any reason, you can do so at any time at this location. 

**7\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information**

You can at any time review and change the information you submitted during registration by visiting the Icovia account preferences section under "My Account" which can be found at http://icovia.com/login.aspx. You must promptly update your information if it changes. 

You can at any time ask to see and have removed any information that we have stored on you, though we reserve the right to charge for this service. If you would like your personal information removed, requests should me made in writing and mailed to the Icovia office (see section 11). Please include your email address and phone number so we can respond to your request. We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that we back up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests that it be removed. 

**8\. Other Information Collectors**

Except as otherwise expressly discussed in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are other members of the Icovia community, other web sites or other parties, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the personal information you disclose to them. 

**9\. Security**

In order to process and protect your credit card details, our payment provider CyberSource uses SSL (secure sockets layer) encryption. 2020 Icovia is also a licensee of GeoTrust, an industry leader providing secure online transactions. 

We use best practices in the 2020 Icovia application and web site to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information but we do not use encryption (such as SSL) or firewalls to further protect the information as it travels across the Internet. This is because we do not believe that, apart from the credit card information processed by CyberSource, the personal information we currently collect warrants such measures and the accompanying loss of speed experienced. You should be aware that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet. 

**10\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

2020 believes in procatively informing its customers and users of changes in its privacy policy and will make every effort to notify its customers in advance of changes that affect them. 

**11\. Contact Information**

If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, the practices of, or your dealings with this site, please contact 2020 at: 

e-mail: 2020icovia.support@2020spaces.com 

Mail: 

2020 Icovia Customer Advocate 

20-20 Technologies 

400 Boulevard Armand Frappier #2020 

Laval, QC H7V 4B4 

Canada 

Telephone: (+1) 866-698-2020 

Fax: (+1) 866-621-2020
